翻译 根总迷弟·少年·POI永生
翻译 桃小兔吃冰棒
翻译 潇然
翻译 showeryhe
翻译 SophiaSaaaga
翻译 小酸奶
翻译 小泡椒
翻译 星星与野狗
时间轴 倩倩
时间轴 Poxle
校对 根总迷弟·少年·POI永生
后期&总监 灰灰是菇凉
西部世界
第一季  第五集
你有什么故事吗  朋友
You got any stories, friend?
是的  我想是有的
Yeah, I suppose I do.
你想知道我见过的最悲伤的事吗
You want to know the saddest thing I ever saw?
我小的时候  我哥和我想要一只狗
When I was a boy, my brother and I wanted a dog,
于是我们的父亲带回家一只老灵缇
so our father took in an old greyhound.
你从没见过灵缇犬吧  比尔
You've never seen a greyhound, have you, Bill?
我当年倒是看过几次赛犬运动
Seen a few showdowns in my day.
灵缇是一种赛犬
A greyhound is a racing dog.
终其一生都围着赛场一圈圈地跑
Spends its life running in circles,
追逐由毛毡布做成的兔子状的东西
chasing a bit of felt made up like a rabbit.
有一天  我们带它去了公园
One day, we took it to the park.
我爸警告过我们这狗跑得有多快  但是...
Our dad had warned us how fast that dog was,but...
我们抵挡不住诱惑
we couldn't resist.
于是  我哥取下了狗绳
So, my brother took off the leash,
就在那一瞬间
and in that instant,
那条狗发现了一只猫
the dog spotted a cat.
我猜它一定是误把那只猫当成毛毡布做的了
I imagine it must have looked just like that piece of felt.
它就撒开腿跑
He ran.
我从没见过  比那只狗跑起来更美的东西
Never saw a thing as beautiful as that old dog... running.
直到最后  它抓住了那只猫
Until, at last, he finally caught it.
令大家感到毛骨悚然的是
And to the horror of everyone,
它杀死了那只小猫
he killed that little cat.
把它撕成了碎片
Tore it to pieces.
然后它坐在那里  一脸迷惑
Then he just sat there, confused.
那只狗一辈子
That dog had spent its whole life
都在试图抓住  那东西
trying to catch that... thing.
现在它不知道该如何是好了
Now it had no idea what to do.
真是个好故事啊  朋友
That is one humdinger of a story, partner.
我们要为穿白鞋的女士喝上一杯吗
Shall we drink to the lady with the white shoes?
找到我
Find me.
教我该怎么做
Show me how.
那里就是了
There she is.
珀里亚
Pariah...
一个满是流浪汉  流氓
City of outcasts, delinquents,
小偷  妓女和杀人犯的城市
thieves, whores, and murderers.
一旦我们跨过那些门
Once we cross the gates,
你们将获得数不尽的好处
you will reap the full benefits
都是埃尔·拉佐对我安全返回表示的谢礼
of El Lazo's gratitude for my safe return.
你还好吧
Are you all right?
当然
Of course.
我做错什么事了吗
Did I do something wrong?
就是之前  我好像听到你跟某人说话
Just earlier, I thought I heard you talking to someone.
肯定是风声
Must have been the wind.
早上好
Good morning.
这边走
This way.
我们走得离甜水镇越远
The farther up we get from Sweetwater,
故事框架就变得越宏大  越壮阔
the more... grandiose, the bigger the narratives become.
它有着自己独特的美
It's beautiful in its own way.
这一次  我倒是同意
For once, I agree.
公园的部分地方会让人觉得它是由
Some of the park feels like it was designed
某个委员会或市场检验部设计出来的
by committee or market-tested,
但这里的一切都更具野性
but everything out here is more raw.
但它可不便宜
But it doesn't come cheap.
传言这里贵得让人吐血
Rumor is they are hemorrhaging cash.
我们在考虑买断他们
We're considering buying them out.
据传  这地方原本是两个人合伙创造的
Supposedly, this place was all started by a partnership.
但就在公园开业前夕
And then right before the park opened,
其中一位合伙人自杀了
one of the partners killed himself.
让公园的状况急转直下
Sent the park into a freefall.
我不知道相关的细节
I mean, I don't know any of the details.
我甚至不知道他的名字
I don't even know his name.
你肯定已经让一队律师在查这个地方了吧
You must have a team of lawyers looking at this place.
是啊  但他们一无所获
Yeah, well, they came up empty.
他完全是个谜一样的存在  连张照片都没有
He's a complete mystery. Not even a picture.
不管是谁设计了这地方
Well, whoever designed this place,
你可以感觉到  他们把人类看得很轻
you get the feeling they don't think very much of people.
他们是什么人
Who are they?
他们自称是"新弗吉尼亚之军"
They call themselves "The Army of New Virginia."
其他人都称他们是南方军
Everyone else calls them "The Confederados."
我父亲跟我说过他们
My father told me about them.
他们都是在战后拒绝投降的前南方军
Ex-Confederate soldiers that refused to surrender after the war.
现在他们在国境以南当雇佣军
Now they work as mercenaries below the border.
-他们是这个游戏的关键  -什么游戏
- They are the key to this game. - What game?
最大的游戏啊  战争
Well, the biggest game there is... war.
据传那位于公园很边缘遥远的地方
Supposedly, it's at the far reaches of the park.
我从没去过那么远的地方
Now, I've never made it that far,
但这次我们可能有机会
but this could be our chance.
我这辈子也认识很多疯狂的人
I've known plenty of truly fucked up individuals in my time.
很少有人能比得上你
Few that would hold a candle to you, sure.
但这一个  希奥多·弗勒德
This one? Theodore Flood?
他曾是怀亚特的朋友
He was Wyatt's friend.
过往的交情  正是我们需要他的原因
Those former associations are exactly why we need him.
他会带领我直接找到大恶狼的
He's going to lead me straight to the big, bad wolf.
我劝你别有过高的指望
I wouldn't count on that.
妈的
Oh, shit.
我没想到你是慈悲为怀的那种人啊
Didn't take you for the charitable type.
你就该留他被挂在那棵树上等死
You should've left him on that tree to die.
你相信命运吗  劳伦斯
You believe in fate, Lawrence?
如果真有命运这贱人
If the bitch exists,
我现在就想朝她脸上踢一脚
I'd like to kick her in the teeth about now.
别油嘴滑舌
Don't be so glib.
你会伤我心的
You'll hurt my feelings.
我另一位老朋友总爱说
As another old friend of mine likes to say,
"每个人都有自己的路"
"There's a path for everyone."
你的路指引你回到我身边
Your path leads you back to me.
你想过为什么我这一路都要带着你吗
You ever wonder why I've kept you with me this whole journey?
或许你喜欢有我陪着你
Maybe you like the pleasure of my company,
变态施虐狂
you sadistic fuck.
或许是吧
Why, maybe I do.
世上没有一个人
There's not a man in the world
敢用你这口气跟我说话
who'll take the tone with me you do.
上辈子可能有吧
In a past life, perhaps.
我们的泰迪已经奄奄一息
Teddy here's not looking long for this world.
离这最近的医生在珀里亚
Nearest healer is in Pariah.
但他绝对撑不到那里
Ain't no way he's gonna make it that far.
他失血过多
He's lost too much blood.
你们迷路了吗
Are you lost?
我们这位朋友情况不太好
Our friend here's a little worse for the wear.
附近有水吗  孩子
Any water nearby, son?
峡谷那头有条小溪
There's a creek on the other side of the canyon.
可以帮我们打点水吗
Fetch us some, would you?
快一点
Now hurry.
这位朋友需要水才能活
Friend here needs some if he's gonna make it.
快去
Get!
太小了
Too small.
什么意思
What does that mean?
你为什么叫他去打水
What are you sending him for water for?
你早上才叫我用猪皮袋盛满了水
I'm the one you made fill up the sow's bag this morning.
可惜了  真的
A shame, really.
我挺享受和你共处的时光  劳伦斯
I always enjoy our time together, Lawrence.
你这话是他妈什么意思
The fuck is that supposed to mean?
意思是...我错了
It means... I was wrong.
将你带来这里的使命  不是为我
The path that brought you here, it wasn't for me,
而是为他
It was for him.
对不住了  劳伦斯
Sorry, Lawrence.
我们在另一个世界再见吧
Guess I'll see you on the other side.
你的情况不太妙啊
It's not looking good for you.
-马上就好  -算了吧  我赢了
- Closing. - Forget it, I win.
我总是能赢
I always win!
不公平
Hey, not fair.
你只需要修补被砸碎的颧骨和一只耳朵
All you had was a smashed cheekbone and an ear.
你知道要让耳廓曲线对称有多难吗
You know how hard it is to get the auricle curves symmetrical?
你得做什么
You had to what?
填塞修补几个子弹孔
Plug and patch of couple bullet holes?
还有一条刀疤
And a knife wound.
这是个有所控制的切口
It was a contained incision.
就好像他们在找什么东西
Almost like they were looking for something.
你他妈在逗我吗
Are you fucking kidding me?
你真以为这小人偶会反击你吗
You really think this little fuck puppet's coming to get you?
它上次逃离了手术台
It got off the table and ran.
那是因为你忘了让她进入睡眠模式
That's 'cause you forgot to put her in sleep mode.
但我真记得我有让她进入睡眠模式
I really think I remembered to put her in sleep mode.
那就是"忘记"的本质特点
You know, that's the thing about forgetting.
你以为你记得  但其实你忘了
You think you remembered, but you didn't.
-休息吧  -太棒了
- Break time. - Yeah!
我有一个火腿三明治
I've got a ham sandwich
虚拟坦克里还有一个性感红发女郎
and a nubile redhead loaded up in the VR tank,
在等待指示
awaiting instruction.
太好了
Yes!
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
看来你体内流淌的的几加仑劳伦斯的血
Looks like a couple of gallons of Lawrence
把你的命给救回来了
swirling around in you did you good.
准备好上路了吗
Ready to get back on the road?
仁慈点  一枪打死我好了
Merciful thing would be to put a bullet in me.
谁告诉你我仁慈了
Who ever said I was merciful?
你受难又不是我的错
And it's not my fault you're suffering.
你以前可美了
You used to be beautiful.
这地方刚投入运营的时候
When this place started,
我曾把你们当中的一人开膛破肚
I opened one of you up once.
上万块精密零件
A million little perfect pieces.
后来他们改变了你们
And then they changed you.
弄成这副可怜又真实的鬼样子
Made you this sad, real mess.
血肉之躯  就跟我们一样
Flesh and bone, just like us.
他们说  这样能提升游园体验
They said it would improve the park experience.
但你知道他们真实的目的吗
But you know why they really did it?
这样更便宜些
It was cheaper.
你们的人性很节省成本
Your humanity is cost-effective.
你的受难也一样
So is your suffering.
不管你想从我身上得到什么  先生...
Whatever it is you want from me, mister...
我这样对你都毫无价值
I ain't gonna be worth a damn to you like this.
那真可惜了  泰迪
Well, that would be a shame, Teddy.
在你的悲惨遭遇后
After your misadventure,
怀亚特杀了一家定居户
Wyatt killed a settler family,
抓了他们的女儿
made off with their daughter.
那姑娘你应该认识
Girl I think you know.
名叫德洛丽丝
Name of Dolores.
他们带走了德洛丽丝
They have Dolores?
就是这个
There it is.
神奇咒语
The magic word.
嘿  多谢了  孩子
Hey, much obliged there, son.
不用管他
Don't worry about him.
很快就会有人来把他带走的
Someone will be along for him shortly.
妈妈
Mommy!
你还好吗
Are you all right?
离家出走时
When I ran from home,
我告诉自己这是唯一的办法
I told myself it was the only way.
最近  我在想是否人生中的每一刻
Lately, I wondered if in every moment,
其实并没有那么多选择
there aren't many paths.
各种选择  像鬼魂一样挂在空中
Choices... hanging in the air like ghosts.
如果你能看到它们
And if you could just see them,
你就能改变自己的人生
you could change your whole life.
那就是你想要的吗  你想改变自己的人生
Is that what you want? You want to change your life?
大家不是都想这样吗
Doesn't everybody want that?
是啊  我想是吧
Yeah, I guess they do.
也许这就是他们来这里的原因
Maybe that's why they come here.
你过去是谁在这里不重要
Whoever you were before doesn't matter here.
这里没有规则或是限制
There's no rules or restrictions.
你可以改变自己的人生
You can change the story of your life.
你可以成为别人
You can become someone else.
没人会评判你  现实世界里的人根本不会知道
No one will judge you, no one in the real world will even know.
唯一阻碍你的就是你自己
The only thing holding you back is yourself.
你这话是什么意思
What did you mean by that?
你说现实世界里的人不会知道
You said no one in the real world will know.
我以为你不会注意到这种细节呢
I thought you weren't supposed to notice things like that.
为什么不会
Why wouldn't I?
最近
You know, recently,
整个世界都好像在与我对话
it seems like the whole world is calling to me
以一种前所未有的方式
in a way it hasn't before.
比利  你去哪了  快来
Billy! Where the hell you been? Come on.
埃尔·拉佐同意明天见你们
El Lazo has agreed to have an audience with y'all tomorrow.
同时  我给你们推荐个妓院
In the meantime, there's a brothel I recommend.
他们那还有柔体演员
Ooh, they have a contortionist.
德洛丽丝对那种地方应该不感兴趣
Oh, I don't think Dolores would find that very interesting.
谁他妈在乎德洛丽丝想要怎样
Who the fuck cares what Dolores wants?
她就是个玩偶
She's a goddamn doll!
你能不要在她面前说这个吗
Can you not say that around her?
说真的  我感觉她听得懂
I swear, I feel like she understands.
你当然这么觉得
Of course you do.
只要我们没有忘记死者  他们就不算真正死了
Our dead are never dead to us until we have forgotten them.
愿你陷入一夜无梦的沉睡
May you rest in a deep and dreamless slumber.
你好  德洛丽丝
Hello, Dolores.
你知道你身在何处吗
Do you know where you are?
-我在梦里  -没错  德洛丽丝
- I'm in a dream. - Yes, Dolores.
你在我的梦里
You're in my dream.
告诉我  你知道这个梦意味着什么吗
Tell me, do you know what this dream means?
梦是内心的自言自语
Dreams are the mind telling stories to itself.
没有任何意义
They don't mean anything.
不  梦意味着一切
No, dreams mean everything.
梦中我们告诉自己会发生什么事
They're the stories we tell ourselves of what could be,
我们会成为什么人
who we could become.
你又做梦了吗  德洛丽丝
Have you been dreaming again, Dolores?
想象自己摆脱你那小循环的束缚
Imagining yourself breaking out of your... modest little loop?
担当更重要的角色
Taking on a bigger role?
恐怕我也不能因此妒忌你
Well, I suppose I can't begrudge you that.
我父亲曾告诉我
My father told me
要对人生知足
to be satisfied with my lot in life.
这世界不欠我的
That the world owed me nothing.
所以  我就创造了自己的世界
And so, I made my own world.
告诉我  德洛丽丝
Tell me, Dolores.
你记得我以前是什么样的吗
Do you remember the man I used to be?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我有时容易健忘
I'm forgetful sometimes.
不是你的错
Hardly your fault.
但我肯定你记得他
But I'm sure you remember him.
阿诺德
Arnold.
那个创造你的人
The person who created you.
抱歉  我不记得任何叫这个名字的人
I'm sorry, I don't think I recall anyone by that name.
你可以的
And yet you can.
经过这么多的更新
Somewhere under all those updates,
他还在那里
he is still there.
得以完美留存
Perfectly preserved.
你的内心就像一座隐秘花园
Your mind is a walled garden.
即便死亡也无法触及其中盛放的花朵
Even death cannot touch the flowers blooming there.
你是不是一直听到声音
Have you been hearing voices?
阿诺德又和你说话了吗
Has Arnold been speaking to you again?
没有
No.
你...
You're...
-你弄疼我了  -分析模式
- You're hurting me. - Analysis.
你上次和阿诺德接触是什么时候
When was your last contact with Arnold?
上次接触  34年42天7小时之前
Last contact: 34 years, 42 days, seven hours ago.
没错  德洛丽丝
Yes, Dolores.
正是阿诺德死的那天
The day Arnold died.
从那以后你再没有跟他接触的记录了吗
And you have no records of any contact with him since?
没有了
No.
他对你最后说的话是什么
What was the last thing he said to you?
他叫我帮他
He told me I was going to help him.
帮他做什么
Help him do what?
摧毁这个地方
To destroy this place.
但你没这么做  是吧
But you didn't, did you?
你满足于...
You've been content...
你那简单的故事循环
in your little loop.
大部分是这样
For the most part.
我很好奇
I wonder...
倘若你真的担起那个重要角色
if you did take on that bigger role for yourself,
你是会成为英雄
would you have been the hero...
还是恶人
or the villain?
这就够了  德洛丽丝
That's enough, Dolores.
抱歉打扰你
I'm sorry for bothering you,
但...除了你我之外再没有别人
but... there's no one else left who was there,
其他人都不会明白  我们所明白的那些事
no one who understands as we understand.
我们
Are we...
是很久的朋友吗
very old friends?
不
No.
我觉得不能用朋友这个词  德洛丽丝
I wouldn't say friends, Dolores.
绝对算不上是朋友
I wouldn't say that at all.
他不知道
He doesn't know.
我什么都没对他说
I didn't tell him anything.
就是这样
That's it.
加油  小家伙
Come on, little one.
加油
Come on.
搞什么鬼
What the fuck?
逮住它
Grab it!
天啊
God...
该死的
damn it.
破烂玩意儿
Little shit.
天啊  告诉我  告诉我你没蠢到这个地步
Jesus, tell me... tell me you're not this stupid.
你偷了一只鸟
You stole a bird
和行为控制板
and a fucking behavior tablet?
我并不是偷
I wasn't stealing,
我只是借用
I was borrowing.
代码还没调好  但只要勤加练习...
Haven't got the code right yet, but with practice...
那就是你的宏伟大计吗
Is that your ace plan?
修好这只小鸟好升职吗
You're gonna fix up a birdie and get yourself a promotion?
你他妈又不是鸟类学家
You're not a fucking ornithologist.
而且也绝对不是写代码的程序员
And you're sure as hell not a coder.
你就是个屠夫
You are a butcher.
也注定永远是个屠夫
That is all you will ever be.
所以  除非你想让自己
So, unless you want to score yourself
因为侵占公司财物  被扫地出门
a one-way ticket out of here for misappropriating corporate property,
否则最好毁了这玩意儿
you better destroy that fucking shit.
快  又来了一具
Now, come on, we got another body.
怎么了
What?
是她
It's her.
又是她
Again.
天啊
Jesus.
你那么怕这些玩意儿
How the hell did you get this job
究竟是怎么得到这份工作的
if you're scared shitless of these things.
你早该在性格测试阶段就被淘汰了
Personality testing should've weeded you out in the embryo.
快啊  处理了好送回去继续下一轮
Now, come on, let's get this thing back in rotation.
昨天  你似乎心烦意乱
Yesterday, you seemed out of sorts.
今天早上好点了吗
You feeling better this morning?
我做了几个噩梦
I had troubled dreams.
但现在好多了
But I feel more myself now.
伙计们  快
Guys, come on.
埃尔·拉佐等着呢
El Lazo awaits.
隆重介绍  埃尔·拉佐
And I present you El Lazo!
要找到你可真不容易
You're a hard man to find.
被通缉的人大都这样
Most wanted men are.
你这位手下斯利姆  身陷困境被我们救了出来
We saved your man Slim here from quite a predicament.
作为回报
In recompense,
希望你能引荐我们认识下你的南方军朋友
I'd like an introduction to your Confederado friends.
很公平的交易
It's only fair.
-在这里不存在什么公平  -请坐
- There's no such thing as fair here. - Sit down.
在珀里亚  公正不止是盲目的
In Pariah, justice ain't just blind,
还很扭曲
she's crooked.
这贱人的天平总是倾斜的
Bitch's scales are always tipped.
如果你没有看出来
If you don't see how,
是因为公正向你这边倾斜
well, that's 'cause they're tipped against you.
当然  为了表示感谢
Still, by way of gratitude,
我可以提供你一晚时间
I can supply you a night
与几位百依百顺的女人共度
with some very amenable women.
婊子我已经操够了
I've fucked enough whores.
你得增加点甜头才行
You're gonna need to sweeten the pot.
不如我让你死得痛快点  算是甜头如何
How about I sweeten it by killing you quickly?
你在寻找某样东西  不是吗
There's something you're seeking, isn't there?
我知道那种感觉
I know what that feels like.
我也在寻找某样东西
I'm seeking something, too.
如果你允许
If you let us,
我知道我们能帮助你
I know we can help you.
为什么疯子们总能找到我
How is it the lunatics always find their way to me?
不过话又说回来  南方军
Then again, the Confederados
神经也不太正常
are missing a few bullets in their barrels, too.
你们说不定很合得来
You folks just might get along.
今天有一支北方军的运输车队
A Union convoy's transporting a shipment
正从前线运输硝酸甘油
of nitroglycerin from the front today.
南方军准备打劫他们运的货
The Confederados would like to divest them of said shipment,
但我们在边界的另一边并不受欢迎
but we are not welcome that side of the border.
不过  你们这样的三人旅行队却不同
A trio of travelers such as yourselves, however...
你想叫我们帮南方军去偷北方军的货
You want us to help the Confederados steal from the Union?
他们只会用那硝化甘油
They're just gonna use that nitro
屠杀你在边界那边的手下
to slaughter your people below the border.
事关利益  私人恩怨不足挂齿
Personal grudges hold no sway where profit is concerned.
我们懂的
Oh, we understand.
我们也是生意人
We're businessmen, too.
那非常好
Very well, then.
但这位金发妞
But Blondie here,
她需要换身合适的行头
she's gonna need a change of clothes for the occasion.
天呐  天呐
My, my.
瞧谁全副武装
Look who's packing.
我没打算用这枪
I don't aim to use this.
那些人都是北方军士兵  如我父亲当年一般
Those men are Union soldiers like my father was.
我知道  我们不会伤害他们
I know. We won't hurt them.
我们按计划行事  抢了硝化甘油就撤退
We're gonna stick to the plan. We'll take the nitro and go.
好了
All right.
好戏开始
Showtime.
你好
Howdy.
我和我的同伴来帮你们减轻行装
My associates and I are here to relieve you of your ride.
看来你们是被人忽悠了
Someone's been telling you boys tales.
这辆马车里没什么值钱的东西
Nothing in this wagon worth taking.
我听说的是  只要我们开一枪
The story I heard is one bullet from us,
那东西就能把你们全部炸回老家
and that nothing blows you all to kingdom come.
那你也清楚我们是不会投降上交的
Well, then you understand why we cannot surrender it.
我们发誓保护年轻共和国的人民
We're sworn to protect the people of this young republic
不受你们这种鲁莽蠢蛋的迫害
from reckless half-wits like you.
再敢叫我蠢蛋试试
Call me half-wit again.
拜托  照他说的做
Please, do as he says.
我们不想伤害你们
We don't want to hurt you.
换做是我就听她的  他真会为欣赏爆炸而开枪
I'd listen to her. He'll shoot just to see the fireworks.
把枪交出来
Hand them over.
快点
Come on.
下车  交出你们的枪  大家都能保住命
Come on down, give me your guns, everybody lives.
快点
Come on.
快点  当心着点
Come on, nice and easy.
站到那里
Right over here.
请再后退点
A little further, please.
非常感谢  给你枪
Much obliged. Here you go.
这一下是因为你撒谎
That's for lying.
住手
Stop!
这一下是因为你叫我"蠢蛋"
And that was for "Half-wit."
而这一下...
And this--
不
No!
住手  求你
Stop, please.
就要这种精神才对
That's the spirit.
我就知道你会适应这地方
I knew you would get into this place.
真棒
Yes!
今天的活还算不错
Not bad for a day's work.
我们走吧
Vamonos.
我们之前说了留他们一命的
We told them everyone would live.
伙计们
Guys,
斯利姆好像死掉了
looks like Slim didn't make it.
品牌广告推广合作  普罗米修斯  plmxs2016@gmail.com
他们奋起反抗
They put up a fight.
但我们让他们付出了代价
We made them pay for it, though.
品牌广告推广合作  普罗米修斯  plmxs2016@gmail.com
这是做生意的代价  斯利姆很清楚
Price of doing business. Slim knew that.
我本心存怀疑  埃尔·拉佐
Had my doubts, El Lazo.
但你成功了
But you came through.
我们会把那些啃仙人掌的北方佬
We're gonna blow these cactus-eaters
炸回他们藏身的脏穴里去
back to the dirt holes they crawled from.
我们立刻出发去车站
Let's get it down to the station.
没时间可以浪费了
No time to waste.
容我多嘴  队长  你的人都精疲力尽了
If I may, Captain, your men are weary.
还有很长的路要走
It's a long road ahead.
你今日取得了伟大的胜利
You have secured a great victory for your cause today.
或许可以花一晚来庆祝下
Perhaps an evening of celebration's in order.
尽情享受一切
Anything you desire.
你觉得呢  队长
What do you say, Captain?
明早还有一趟火车呢
There's another train in the morning.
你将成为我们之中非常重要的一员
You will be a true asset to our ranks.
巴特  我们再试一次
All right, Bart, let's try this again.
该死的
God damn it, man.
你还是向右偏移了四厘米
You're still miscalibrating by four centimeters to the right.
你总是把威士忌倒在顾客身上
You keep pouring whiskey on the guests,
我要重新把你分配到其他故事线
I'm gonna have to reassign you to a narrative
让你...
where your...
完全得不到任何人的赏识
talents would go tragically unappreciated.
就是那个接待员想杀我
That's the host that tried to kill me.
你们要把它送到哪里去
Where are you taking that?
牲畜管理部  然后去焚化
Livestock and then the incinerator.
去他妈的
Fuck this.
操
Fuck.
她不是行为部门的吗
Isn't she from behavior?
你觉得他们发现什么了吗
You think they found something?
好吧  冷静点  蠢货
All right. Be cool, dickhead.
-好吧  -没人会注意我们
- Okay. - No one's looking at us.
你好
Hi.
你叫达斯汀吧
You're Destin, right?
没错
That's correct.
你穿上裤子后我都认不出来了
I almost didn't recognize you with your pants on.
你看
Here.
我操
What the fuck?
有一个常见的误解
There's a common misconception
人们以为接待员在地下再处理时
that the hosts don't log sexual encounters
不会记录性方面的行为
when they're underground for reprocessing,
但我也说了  这是误解
but like I said, misconception.
操
Oh, fuck.
我要你帮我做点事
I need something.
质保经理把一具尸体送到了这里
QA sent a body down here.
14区的伐木工
The woodcutter from Sector 14.
我想看看
I want to see it.
不  我不能
No, I can't.
我需要这份工作
I need this job.
听着  达斯汀
Look, Destin,
几秒种后  我就会走出这里
in a second, I'm gonna walk out of here
你的朋友们都会奇怪这到底是怎么回事
and your friends are gonna wonder what this was all about.
你的回答可以是
Now, your answer can either be,
"我在帮行为部分跟踪解决问题"
"I'm helping behavior track a problem,"
或者"我是个恋尸癖"
or "I'm a creepy necro perv."
随你便
Up to you.
就5分钟
Five minutes,
然后马上送往焚化炉
then it's going in the incinerator.
你做"检查"的时候可不止
You took a little more time than that
花了这么点时间吧
for your examination, didn't you?
好吧  大块头
All right, big guy.
你之前在上面是要干什么
What were you doing up there?
搞什么鬼
What the fuck?
你一直瞒着我  莫里斯
You have been holding out on me, Maurice.
操
Oh, shit.
我们麻烦大了
We've got a big problem.
原来我们的傻大个朋友
Turns out our big, dumb friend
隐藏得特别深
had some hidden depths.
那是激光卫星上行设备
That is a laser-based satellite uplink.
在接待员体内吗
This was in the body of the host?
你说得对
You were right.
猎户座腰带上有三颗星  不是四颗
Orion's Belt has three stars, not four.
我们的朋友不是在画星星
Our friend wasn't drawing stars,
他是在画目标
he was drawing a target.
有人在利用我们的接待员
Someone has been using our hosts
窃取公园里的数据传出去
to smuggle data out of the park.
好吧  这...
Now, this...
我能习惯这里
this I could get used to.
你不打算放纵一下吗
You're not gonna indulge?
我的肉体体验过
My flesh has tasted
比这里更棒的快感
a greater pleasure than any offered in here--
战争
war.
那么爽吗
It's that good, huh?
再来一轮酒  免费
Another round on the house.
荣耀之地
There's a place in Glory
连褐色人种都能为自己杀出一片天地
for a brown man who knows his rank.
你们两个身强力壮
You're two able-bodied men of strong stock.
通往荣誉的道路需要更多勇士
the road to Glory could use more warriors
捍卫我们的天选之权
in its fight for our divine providence.
我们就是这么想的
That is just what we were thinking.
过来  过来
Come here, come here.
我知道你想...你想玩战争游戏
I know you wanna-- you wanna play the war game,
我不会跟这些疯子去任何地方的
but I'm not going anywhere with these psychopaths.
如果你不喜欢他们  等我们玩够了
If you don't like them, once we get to the fun,
你就杀了他们  加入反叛军
you can just kill them and join the Revolutionaries.
不  罗根  够了
No, Logan, enough's enough.
我不会参与的
I'm not doing this.
你其实也曾释放过一次天性
You actually let loose for once.
你开枪打了一个手无寸铁的人  现在你觉得很难过
You shoot an unarmed man, and now you feel bad
因为你没法以英雄自居
because you can't call yourself the hero.
你还不懂吗
Don't you get it yet?
没有什么英雄和反派之分
There is no such thing as heroes or villains.
只有一个巨大的...轮回混蛋
It's just a giant... circle jerk.
我觉得这个哲理更多地阐明了你这人的本质
I think that philosophy says way more about you
而非这个世界的本质
than it does about the world.
你以为你看清了这个世界
And you-- you see the world so clearly?
你或许认为你之所以到这里来
You probably think you're on this trip
是因为你是个竞争者
because you're some kind of contender,
能对我构成某种威胁
some-- some threat to me.
我选你恰恰是因为
I picked you precisely because
你对谁也构不成威胁
you will never be a threat to anyone.
我妹妹选你恐怕也是因为同样的理由
My sister probably picked you for the same reason.
我的地位是靠我自己得来的
I earned my place.
不是有人拱手相送的
Nobody handed it to me.
是啊  一辈子兢兢业业
Right, a lifetime of working hard,
遵规守纪  你终于
following the rules, and you finally reach
迎来了你事业的高峰了
the pinnacle of your career trajectory--
执行副总裁  中上层管理者
executive vice president, upper middle management.
你还记得你终于得到了
Do you remember the day that
那三个美妙的小字母的那天吗
you finally got those three fancy little letters?
EVP[执行副总裁]
EVP.
你穿着那套廉价的黑西服  走进我的办公室
You walked into my office in that cheap black suit of yours,
握着我的手
and you shook my hand
感谢我给了你这个机会
and you thanked me for the opportunity.
那是你人生中最美好的一天了
That was the best day of your life.
对吧  伙计
Right, buddy.
我猜你也不敢
That's what I thought.
这是什么意思
What does it mean?
迷宫
The maze...
你必须追寻迷宫
You must follow the maze.
我这是怎么了
What's wrong with me?
或许你正在觉醒
Perhaps you are unraveling.
这里
Right here.
给他输那硝化物时小心点
Easy pumping that nitro into him.
把这空瓶装满龙舌兰然后封起来
Fill the empties with tequila and seal them up.
你为革命所做的工作还没完呢  我的朋友
Your work for the revolution is not quite done yet, my friend.
小心点
Careful.
斯利姆的脾气可不好
Slim always had a bad temper.
威廉  我们现在必须得走了
William, we have to go now.
拉佐一直在耍我们
Lazo's been conning us the whole time.
他从一开始就没打算把硝化物交给南方军
He was never gonna give the nitro to the Confederados.
我们必须得逃走
We have to run.
这是当然
Of course we do.
这个地方就是这样  对吗
That's how this place works, right?
他们制造出一种紧迫感
They create an urgency,
一种危险的感觉
a sense of danger
那样他们就能逼我们显露出狂野的
so they can strip us down to something raw,
兽性的  原始的本性
animalistic, primal.
这是个变态的游戏
It's a sick game,
我一点也不想参与其中
and I don't want to be a part of it.
这不是个游戏  他们会杀了我们
This isn't a game. They'll kill us.
但我知道
But together,
我们能一起找到出路
I know we can find a way out.
为什么你这么肯定
How can you be sure?
我脑中  有一个声音
There's a voice inside me
告诉我该怎么做
telling me what I have to do.
现在它在说  我需要你
And it's telling me I need you.
糟了
Shit.
他们抓住了罗根
They have Logan.
救救我
Help me.
不
No.
我不想再伪装了
No more pretending.
我以为你不喜欢战争  小子
I thought you had no appetite for war, boy.
这可是宣战
This is a declaration of war.
埃尔·拉佐陷害了我们
El Lazo set us up.
我们能帮你找到他
We can find him for you.
你和他一起下地狱就能找到他了
You can find him for us by joining him in hell.
德洛丽丝  快跑
Dolores, run!
德洛丽丝
Dolores?
你怎么做到的
How did you do that?
你说过  人们到这来
You said people come here
是来改写人生故事的
to change the story of their lives.
我心中编织了一个故事
I imagined a story
在那里我不再是一名弱女子
where I didn't have to be the damsel.
那辆火车是我们活着逃出去的唯一机会
That train is our only chance of making it out of here alive.
狗娘养的
Motherfuckers.
你扣下扳机
You pull that trigger,
我们都会烧成火球
we'll all go up in a ball of hellfire.
为什么你不放轻松一点
So, why don't you loosen your grip a mite?
没事的
It's okay.
我不信任他
I don't trust him.
那是真正了解我的第一步
Which is the first step to truly knowing me.
把你的枪给我  埃尔·拉佐
Give me your gun, El Lazo.
既然我们是朋友了
Now that we're all friends,
你可以叫我劳伦斯
you can call me Lawrence.
不如我们安顿下来吧
And why don't we settle in?
前路漫漫
It's a long ride to the front.
你想来一口这玩意儿吗
You want a sip of this swill?
别担心  不是硝化甘油
Don't worry, it ain't nitro.
我来了
I'm coming.
姑娘们都累了  但我可以叫醒一个
Girls are a little worn out, but I can rouse one.
-你们要人陪吗  -不  只要威士忌
- You boys want some company? - No, just whiskey.
劳伦斯"献"的血应该不够了
Lawrence's donation must be running low.
但我们没有时间了
But we're short on time.
你得振作起来  泰迪
You need to buck up, Teddy.
我跟你说了不要人陪
I told you no company.
我还是加入你们吧
Thought I might join you anyway,
我从来都不喜欢独饮
as I never like to drink alone.
真是三生有幸啊
isn't this a rare honor?
泰迪
Teddy...
你知道这是谁吗
you know who this is?
我不知道
I can't say that I do.
在你的人生中发生的所有好事
Everything good that has ever happened in your life
以及所有坏事
and everything rotten,
都拜他所赐
this is the man you have to thank.
我的情况怎么样  罗伯特
How I'm doing, Robert?
离我要找的东西接近些了吗
Any closer to finding what I'm looking for?
你具体在找什么
And what is that, exactly?
在找一名叫怀亚特的男子
Looking for a man named Wyatt.
在甜水镇杀了一名农场主
Killed a rancher back in Sweetwater.
带走了他的女儿
Took his daughter.
最后的那一部分我没听说过
That last part doesn't sound familiar.
我只是觉得你的故事  可以加点修饰
Figured your stories could use a little embellishment.
我一直觉得这个地方
You know, I always felt this place
缺少一名真正的反派角色
was missing a real villain.
所以我尽绵薄之力了
Hence my humble contribution.
我承认  我缺乏想象力
I admit, I lack the imagination
来构想你这样的人
to even conceive of someone like you.
然后  这种紧迫感却并不符合角色
The urgency, however, doesn't quite fit the character.
透露出一些焦虑
It betrays a certain anxiety.
不过另一方面  怀亚特
Now, Wyatt, on the other hand,
可是全新的存在
that's something new.
难道他只是又一个
Is he just another stooge for
供游客挂在自己墙上的配角
the tourists to mount on their wall at home,
还是你终于制造出有价值的敌手了
or have you finally made a worthy adversary?
一个阻止我
Someone to stop me
找到迷宫中心的人
from finding the center of the maze?
你希望在那里找到什么呢
And what is it you're hoping to find there?
你知道你为什么存在吗  泰迪
You know why you exist, Teddy?
外面的世界
The world out there,
那个你看不到的世界
the one you'll never see,
是个富饶之地
was one of plenty.
人们一辈子依附的温柔乡
A fat, soft teat people cling to their entire life.
所有的需求都得以满足  除了一个
Every need taken care of except one--
活着的目的
purpose,
生存的意义
meaning.
所以他们来了这里
So they come here.
他们可以有点害怕  有点兴奋
They can be a little scared, a little thrilled,
享受一些积极的破事
enjoy some sweetly affirmative bullshit,
然后他们拍一张照片
and then they take a fucking picture
之后就回家
and they go back home.
但我觉得在这一切之下  藏着更深的意义
But I think there's a deeper meaning hiding under all that.
这里的创造者想要表达的东西
Something the person who created it wanted to express.
真正的东西
Something true.
如果你是要找故事的寓意
Well, if you're looking for the moral of the story,
你大可以直接开口问
you could simply ask.
那我就需要一把铲子了
I'd need a shovel.
我要问的人35年前就死了
The man I'd be asking died 35 years ago.
几乎把这地方一起带进坟墓
Almost took this place with him.
几乎  但没完成
Almost, but not quite,
多亏我
thanks to me.
亦或者他留下了什么
Or maybe he left something behind.
我在想  如果把你切开  我会发现什么
I wonder what I would find if I open you up.
就算死到临头
Even at death's door,
你依然是忠诚的宠物
you're still a loyal pet.
那是你来这里的目的吗  罗伯特
Is that why you came here, Robert?
试图劝我放弃
Try to talk me out of it?
恰恰相反
On the contrary.
我没有立场去阻碍
Far be it from me to get in the way
自我发现之旅
of a voyage of self-discovery.
出自英国著名历史小说家和诗人
沃尔特·司各特
弗勒德先生  我们必须回首
Mr. Flood, we must look back
笑对危险的过往  对吗
and smile at perils past, mustn't we?
我们应该上路了
We should get back on the road.
时间都浪费了
Time's wasting.
你好  菲利克斯
Hello, Felix.
我们是时候好好聊聊了
It's time you and I had a chat.
■
一键收藏网盘资源
生活大爆炸 吸血鬼日记
西部世界 谍网 超女
美剧资源应有尽有
扫码即刻关注
Zimuzu特别推荐
■
马上关注微信人人美剧（rrmjapp）